Gael Greene Magazine Collection 1968-2008 MSS.392
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Magazines
  - December 10, 1990 - October 28, 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
    -12/10/90. NYM, Vol23, Issue 48, "Chompin' At Savoy" insatiiable critc (Savoy) P.62
    -12/17/90. NYM, Vol.23, issue 49, "The Hungry Eye" insatiable critic (Cookbooks). P.64
    -12/24-31/90. NYM, Vol.23, Issue 50, "-12/10/90. NYM, Vol23, Issue 48, "Chompin' At Savoy" insatiiable critc (Savoy) P.62
    -12/24-31/90. NYM, Vol.23, Issue 50, "Treasures of NY: David Bouley Magic Chef" P.65
    -1/7/91. v. 24 # 1 (Abilene Cafe, Adrienne, Alison on Dominick Street, Alo Alo, Arqua, Arturo's, Auntie Yuan, Aureole, Ballroom, Bar du Theatre, Barolo, Between the Bread, Big City Diner, Bouley, Box Tree, Broadway Grill, Buckaroo's Bar & Rotisserie, Cafe Iguana, Carmine's,Chez Louis, Chin Chin Coco Pazzo, Contrapunto, Da Umberto, Edwardian Room, Eldorado, Petit, Felidia, 44, Four Seasons, Giorgio Cafe, Gotham Bar & Grill, Greene Street Cafe, Grolier, Hard Rock Cafe, Hudson River Club, John's Pizza, Jour er Nuit, Kwong and Wong, La Boheme, La Cite, Lafayette, La Grenouille, La Jumelle, La Maison du Chocolat, Laura Belle, Le Bar Bat, Le Bernardin, Le Cirque, Le Comptoir, Le Madri, Le PErigord, Les Halles, Lola, Lucky Strike,Lutece, Madras Woodlands, March, Mark's, Mesa Grill, Mickey Mantle's, Mondrian, Nick & Eddie's, Orso, Palio, Paramount, Piatti Pronti, Pierre's, Planet Hollywood, Primavera, Prix Fixe, Rainbow Room, Remi, Sea Grill, Serendipity, Sette Mezzo, Shun Lee Palace, Sign of the Dove, SoHo Kitchen and Bar, Sylvia's, Tai Hong Lau, Tatou, Trattoria dell'Arte, TriBeCa Grill, Trixies, 21, Union Square Cafe, Vince & Eddie's, Vucciria, Windowa on the World, Yellowfinger's di Nuovo, Zarela). "Ask Gael New Year, New Hot Spots." p. 20
    -2/18/91. v. 24 # 7 (Mesa Grill). "The Corn is Blue." p. 58
    -3/4/91. v. 24 # 9 (La Colombe d'Or, '21' Club). "The Return of the Natives." p. 68 & 72
    -3/11/91. v. 24 # 10 (Ed Debevic's). "Burps on Broadway." p. 62
    -3/18/91. v. 24 # 11 (Mondrian, March). "Back to the Future." p. 56-57
    -4/1/91. v. 24 # 13 (Corrado). "Venice, Anyone?" p. 56-57
    -4/15/91. v. 24 # 15 (Rex, Shark Bar). "The Joy of Rex." p. 60-63
    -5/6/91. v. 24 # 18 (Serendipity III, Greene Street, Japanese on Hudson, Joe's Bar & Grill, La Cité, The Soho Kitchen, Tatou, Brasserie, Prix Fixe, The '21' Club, Alison on Dominick, Malvasia, Tavern on the Green, City Cafe, Cafe Luxembourg, Carmine's, Symphony Cafe, Stage Deli, Andiamo, Nick and Eddie, Petrossian, L'Omnibus, San Domenico, Aquavit, Cafe des Artistes, Cafe Crocodile, Box Tree Kitchens, Houlihan's, TGI Friday's, El Torito, Lindy's, Tequilla Willie's, Ground Round, Cavanagh, Toots Shor, Desert Rose, Water Club, Dawat, Darbar). "Eating Out: Sales & Bargains." p. 26-31
    -5/27/91. v. 24 # 21 (Zen Palate, Jewel of India). "Original Zen." p. 58-60
    -6/17/91. v. 24 # 23 (The Sign of the Dove). "A Dove Affair." p. 56
    -7/1-8/91. v. 24 # 26 (Amazon Club, Boathouse Cafe, Water Club, Edward Moran, Steamers Landing, Liberty Cafe, Harbour Lights, World Yacht). "On the Water." p. 46-50
    -7/22/91. v. 24 # 28 (Water's Edge, R.H. Tugs, Arthur's Landing, Shanghai Red's Lincoln Harbor, Paddy McGees, Coyote Grill, Lobster Box, Anna's Harbour Restaurant, River Café). "Shore Things." p. 34-38
    -8/12/91. v. 24 # 31 (Barolo, Eze, Vince & Eddie's). "Gardens of Delight." p. 65-66
    -8/26/91 NYM, Vol.24, issue.33, "Hangin with the Homeboys" (Mazzei) P.126-127
    -9/30/91. v. 24 # 38 (Le Bar Bat, Le Pescadou). "Best Bats." p. 58-59
    -10/7/91. v. 24 # 39 (Mimosa, Cucina & Co). "Grub Med." p. 82-84
    -10/21/91. v. 24 # 41 (Chiam, China Grill). "The China Syndrome." p. 86-89
    -10/28/91. v. 24 # 42 (Lespinasse). "The Gray Eminence." p. 77 of NY: David Bouley Magic Chef" P.65
  - November 11, 1991 - November 16, 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 16)
    -11/11/91. v. 24 # 44 (Planet Hollywood). "Planet of the Grapes." p. 110-112
    -11/25/91. v. 24 # 46 (Shaliga Thai). "Thai Me Up, Thai Me Down." p. 107
    -12/2/91. v. 24 # 47 (Lora, Cucina). "California Dreaming." p. 142-144
    -12/23-30/91. v. 24 # 50 (The Food of New York). "Oral History." p. 57-64
    -12/23-30/91. v 24 #50 (The Food of New York). "The Heavies." p, 114-115
    -12/23-30/91. v. 24 #50 (The Food of New York). "The Ultimate Restaurant Guide.", p. 116-154
    -1/27/92. v. 25 # 4 (Afghan Kebab House, Alison on Dominick Street, An American Place, Le Bar Bat, Beekman 1766 Tavern, Le Bernardin, Big Wong, Boogies Diner, Bouley, Brasserie, Broadway Grill, Cafe des Artistes, La Caravelle, Les Celebrities, Chefs Cuisiniers Club, Chez Josephine, Chiam, Chin Chin, China Grill, Le Cirque, Coco Pazzo, Coffee Shop, La Colombe d'Or, Le Comptoir, Da Umberto, Ed Debevic's, Elaine's, Empire Diner, Fisher & Levy, Fishin Eddie, 44, Four Seasons, Golden Unicoen, Gotham Bar & Grill, Greene Street Cafe, La Grenouille, Hudson River Club, Jean Lafitte, Jewel of India, Joe Allen, JoJo, Jour et Nuit, Lespinasse, Lucky Strike, Lutece, Le Madri, Manhattan Ocean Club, Mark's, Mazzei, Mesa Grill, La Metairie, Metropolis Cafe, Mezzanine, Mickey Mantle's, Mimosa, Mondrian, Montrachet, Mulholland Drive Cafe, Nosmo King, Ollie's, Orso, Palio, Periyali, Petrossian, Pig Heaven, Planet Hollywood, Prix Fixe, Provence, Rainbow Room, Remi, Restaurant Raphael, Rex, River Cafe, Sandro's, Scores, Sea Grill, Shaliga Thai Cuisine, Shun Lee Cafe, Shun Lee Palace, Sidewalkers', Sign of the Dove, SoHo Kitchen & Bar, Stringfellows Presents Pure Platinum, Supper Club, Sylvia's, Tang Tang, Tatou, Trattoria, Trattoria dell'Arte, TriBeCa Grill, Tropica, "21", Two Boots, Vong and Kwong, World Yacht Cruises, Zen Palate). "Ask Gael: The Tastes and Trends of Brave New '92." p. 43-49
    -2/17/92. v. 25 # 7 (Quilted Giraffe, Japonica). "Japan Noshing." p. 54-55
    -2/24/92. v. 25 # 8 (Park Avenue Cafe). "Little Chop Around the Corner." p. 127
    -3/2/92. v. 25 # 9 (May We, Zoe). "May Oui." p. 50 & 53
    -3/16/92. v. 25 # 11 (Country Club, Supper Club, B. Smith's, Rex, WunderBar). "Club Scouting." p. 65-67
    -3/23/92. v. 25 # 12 (Patric). "Patric's Day." p. 64
    -4/20/92. v. 25 # 16 (West Broadway, Wilson's, Cafe Tabac). "Lullaby of West Broadway." p. 86 &88
    -4/27/92. v. 25 # 17 (Le Cirque, Mesa Grill, Union Square Cafe, Lespinasse, Four Seasons, Jo-Jo). "It's Easy Eating Green." p. 46-47
    -5/4/92. v. 25 # 18 (Steak Frites, Rocco). "Beyond Meat and Frites." p. 74 &76
    -6/1/92. v. 25 # 22 (Boom, Felix). "Boom Town." p. 54-55
    -10/5/92. v. 25 # 39 (Banana Cafe). "I Can't Hear You, I've Got a Banana in my Ear." p. 88
    -10/12/92. v. 25 # 40 (San Pietro, Caffe Florence). "Garlic Press." p. 62-63
    -10/19/92. v. 25 # 41 (Arizona 206, Follonico). "Hot and Sweet." p. 90-91
    -10/26/92. v. 25 # 42 (Brasserie des Theatres, Chop Suey Looey's Litchi Lounge). "Two for the Show." p. 80-81
    -11/9/92. v. 25 # 44 (Lipstick Cafe, Au Cafe, Bar Pitti, Cafe Cinema Graphique, Cafe 400). "Small Talk." p. 64-65
    -11/16/92. v. 25 # 45 (Hosteria Fiorella, Zoe). "The Most Happy Fiorella." p. 70-71
  - November 30, 1992 - June 21, 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 17)
    -11/30/92. v. 25 # 47 (Four Seasons, Chanterelle). "Out of the Pool and into the Grill." p. 106-108
    -12/7/92. v. 25 # 48 (Oggi Domani, Restaurant Two Two Two). "Eminent Domani." p.62-63
    -12/14/92. v. 25 # 49 (One Fifth Avenue). "One Fish Avenue." p. 84-85
    -12/21-28/92. v. 25 # 50 (Le Cirque). "Sirio Maccioni: The Ringmaster of Le Cirque." p. 78-80
    -1/4/93. V. 26 # 1 (Afghan Kebab House, Afghan Tea Room, Alison on Dominick Street, American Festival Cafe, Andiamo, Apple, Arizona 206, Bananna Cafe, Baraonda, Barbetta, Becco, Le Bernardin, Boom, Bouley, The Brasserie, Brasserie des Theatres, Broadway Grill, Cafe des Artistes, Cafe 400. Cafe Tabac, Caffe Florence, Cal's, Canastel's, Carmine's, Carmine's Takeout, Century Cafe, Chiam, China Grill, Le Cirque, City Cafe, Coco Pazzo, Coffee Shop, La Colombe d'Or, Il Corallo, Dakota Bar & Grill, David K's Noodle Road, Elaine's, Felix,, Fishin Eddie, Five Oaks, Follonico, 44, Four Seasons, Golden Unicoen, Gotham Bar & Grill, Gus' Place, Les Halles, Hosteria Fiorella, Isabella's, JoJo, Kin Khao, Lespinasse, Lipstick Cafe, Lolabelle, Lucky Strike, Luxe, May We, Mesa Grill, La Metairie, Nell's, Nosmo King, Odeon, Oggi Domani, One Fith Avenue, Palio, Park Bistro, Peter Luger, Petrossian, Prix Fixe, Rainbow Room, Raou;'s, Raoul's Brasserie, Restaurant Two Two Two, Sfuzzi, Shanghai 1933, Shun Lee Cafe, Shun Lee Palace, The Sign of the Dove, Silverado, SoHo Kitchen, Soleil, Sparks Steakhouse, Steak Frites, Tang Pavilion, Tenth Street Lounge, Trattoria Dell'Arte, Triangolo, Tribeca Grill, Tropica, "21', Union Square Cafe, Villa Lulu, Vince and Eddies, Vong, West Broadway, Wilson's, Zen Palate, Zoe.) "Ask Gael: More News Than You'd Think For '93." p. 22-31
    -1/25/93. v.26 #4 (Vong, One Fifth Avenue). "The Vong Show." p. 52-53
    -2/1/93. v. 26 #5 (Soleil, La Gauloise). "A Couple of Swells." p. 48 & 50
    -2/8/93. v.26 #6 (Baraonda, Frontiere). "Go Chic and Ye Shall Find."p. 60-61
    -2/15/93. v. 26 #7 (Le Chantilly, City Cafe). "Miracle on 57th Street." p. 54-55
    -3/1/93. v. 26 # 9 (Cascabel, Indochine). "Lafayette, They Are There." p.108-109
    -3/15/93. v. 26 # 11 (Taste of Hong Kong). "Friendly Fire." p.58
    -3/29/93. v. 26 # 13 (Le Cirque). "Petit Pan." p. 75-76
    -4/12/93. v. 26 # 15 Chinese Evolution (Triple Eight Palace, New Hong Kong City, Tai Hong Lau, Kam Chueh, Oriental Garden, Oriental Pearl, New Chao Chow, Chinese Country Kitchen, Goody's, Taipei Big Rice Bowls, Penang Cuisine Malaysia, Big Wong, Bo Ky, Wing Wong, China Fun, Tang Tang, Ollie's Noodle Shop & Grill, Golden Unicorn, Jing Fong, Tai Hong Lau Sun Ko Shing, Shun Lee Cafe, Harbor Seafood, Jade Palace, Shun Lee Palace, Shun Lee, Chiam, Shaghai 1933, David K's Noodle Road, Hunan Fifth Avenue, Chin Chin, Pig Heaven, Taste of Hong Kong, Empire Szechuan Gourmet). "Chinese Evolution." p. 30-41
    -4/19/93. v. 26 # 16 (Paul Bocuse). "Dinner of the Century." (2) p.138 & 140
    -4/26/93. v. 26 # 17 (Blue Ribbon, Hi-Life Restaurant & Lounge) "The Tao of Pu Pu." (2) p. 64-65
    -5/3/93. v. 26 # 18 (Home). "Halfway Home." p. 62
    -5/17/93. v. 26 #20 (Colors). "Flying Colors." p. 74-75
    -5/31/93. v. 26 #22 (Luma, Nosmo King). "The Organic Verses." p. 50-53
    -6/14/93. v. 26 #24 (Daniel). "The Book on Daniel." p. 63
    -6/21/93 NYM
  - June 28, 1993 - January 10, 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    -6/28-7/5/93. v. 26 #26 (Baraonda, Sign of the Dove, Arcadia, May We, Jour et Nuit, New World Grill, Coffee Shop, Felix, Isabella's, Au Cafe, Time Cafe, Stanhope Terrace Cafe). "Street Food. p. 78-106
    -7/12/93. v. 26 #27 (East Hampton Point, 95 School Street, Fresno). "Barbarians at the Plate." p. 47-48
    -7/19/93. v. 26 #28 (Main Street, Cafe One Fifth). "The World is My Oyster." p.46-47
    -8/2/93. v. 26 # 30 (Quaglino's, Le Pont de la Tour, Sea-Shell, Lanesborough Hotel, Daphne's, The Ivy, The Canteen, Christopher's, San Lorenzo, Planet Hollywood). "True Brit." (2) p. 43-47
    -9/13/93 NYM
    -9/20/93 v. 26 # 37 (Fiorello's, La Cité) Seconds p. 62
    -9/27/93. v. 26 # 38 (Lutece). "My Dinners with Andre." p. 62-63
    -10/4/93. v. 26 #39 (Sette Moma). "Moma Mia! p. 103
    -10/11/93. v. 26 #40 (The Gotham Bar & Grill). "Grill Crazy." p. 72-74
    -10/18/93. v. 26 #41 (Le Taxi, Symphony Cafe). "Yellow Fever." p. 118-119
    -10/25/93. v. 26 #42 (Mad 61). "Dressing on the Side." p. 93
    -11/8/93. v. 26 #44 (Morton's of Chicago, Eastern Seafood Company). "To Sirloin with Love." p. 72-73
    -11/15/93. v. 26 # 45 (Picholine, Harley Davidson Cafe). "Olive and Kicking." p. 82-83
    -11/22/93. v. 26 # 46 (Matthew's, Demi). "The Gospel According to Matthew's." p.68-70
    -12/13/93. v. 26 #49 (Fresco). "Penne From Heaven." p. 78
    -12/20-27/93. v. 26 # 50 (VIX Cafe, SushiHatsu, Kurumazushi, Shun Lee Palace, New Hong City, Goody's, Jerry's, Union Square Cafe, Mesa Grill, Le Madri, Mad.61, Lespinasse, Matre d'Michael, Tong, Maison du Chocolat, Remi, Alison on Dominick). "The Best of New York" p. 83, 85, 88, 94, 104, 109,112, 117, 120, 126, & 139
    -1/3/94. Vol 27 no. 1 (Peter Luger, Morton's, Sparks, Smith & Wollensky, Palm Restaurant, Cité, Post House, Old Homestead, Pen & Pencil, Post House, Ruth's Chris, American Festival Cafe, Les Halles, Ben Benson's, Wally's and Joseph's, Pietro's, Christ Cella, Gallagher's, Opus II, China Grill, 21, Mesa Grill, Coco Pazzo, Kam Chueh, Isabella's, Coffee Shop). "Sizzling Steak Wars." p. 25-33
    -1/10/94. v. 27 # 2 (Bolo). "Oil of Olé." p. 43
  - January 24, 1994 - December 12, 1994 (Box 19)
    -1/24/94. v. 27 # 4 (Christer's). "The Seventh Salmon." p. 75-76
    -1/31/94. v. 27 # 5 (Les Célèbrités). "The Sweet Smell of Excess." p. 58-59
    -2/7/94. v. 27 # 6 (American Festival Cafe, Anglers & Writers, Aureole, Baluchis, James Beard Foundation, Bolo, Bouley, Buddha Bar, Christer's, Cité, Coco Pazzo, Din-Tai-Fone of Taipei, Eastern Seafood Co., Fiorello's Roman Cafe, Flowers, Fresco, Gotham Bar and Grill, William Greenberg Jr. Desserts, Home, Iridium, Isabella's, Jing Fong, John;s Pizzeria, JoJo, Kelley and Ping, Kin Khao, La Goulue, La Palette, Le Chantilly, Le Cirque, Le Colonial, Le Taxi, Lespinasse, mad.61, Main street, March, Matthew's, MercBar, Mesa grill, Mickey Mantle's Sports Restaurant, One Fifth Avene, Cafe One Fifth, Osteria al Doge, Park Avalon, Park Avenue Cafe, Picholine, Planet Hollywood, Rainbow Promenade Bar, Rainbow Room, Rainbow & Stars, Red River Grill, Restaurant Daniel, Restaurant Two Two Two, San Domenico, Serendipity, Sfuzzi, Shaliga Thai Cuisine, Shun Lee, Shun Lee Cafe, SoHo Kitchen and Bar, Symphony Cafe, Tavola, Thai Friends Restaurant, Triple Eight Palace, Vince & Eddie's, Vix Cafe, Vong, Zen Palate). "Ask Gael." p. 40-53
    -2/14/94. v. 27 # 7 (Baluchi's). "Fire and Rice." p. 64
    -3/14/94. v. 27 # 11 (Kwanzaa, Cafe Beulah, Soul Fixins', Birdland, Virgil's, Emily's, Shark Bar, Mr. Leo, Jezebel, The Pink Tea Cup, Zacki's, Jamaican Hot Pot, Sylvia's, Well's, Cotton Club). "Soul Food Now." p. 58-63
    -3/21/94. v. 27 # 12 (Patria, Park Avalon). "Pan-Am Games." p. 68-69
    -3/28/94. v. 27 # 13 (Judson Grill)."Razzmatazz on Swing Street." p. 113-114
    -4/11/94. v. 27 # 15 (Cascabel, Alison on Dominick). "Shanks for the Memories." p. 62-63
    -4/18/94. v. 27 # 16 (Martini's, Mustang Grill). "Blithe Spirits." p. 111-112
    -4/25/94. v. 27 # 17 (River Café)."Of Thyme and the River." p. 90-91
    -5/2/94. v. 27 # 18 (Virgil's Real Barbeque). Insatiable: "Amazing Grease." p. 80
    -5/23/94. v. 27 # 21 (Phoenix Garden, Fu's, Lucky Cheng's). Insatiable: "Wok of Ages." P. 78
    -5/30/94. v. 27 # 22 (Match). Insatiable: "Match Ado." p. 66-67
    -6/6/94. v. 27 # 23 (Silk, Toast). "Silk Roots." p. 60-61
    -6/20/94. v. 27 # 24 (C.T.). "Cafe un deux Troisgros." p. 80-81
    -7/11/94. v. 27 # 27 (Campagna). "Ciao Down." p. 51-52
    -7/25/94. v. 27 # 29 (La Mère Poulard, Gauguin, Caviateria Champagna, Caviar bar, China Fun, Shaan, Josie's, Jerry's). "Reality Bites." p. 50, 55-56
    -8/22/94. v. 27 # 33 (Privé, Gilbert Le Coze). "The Restaurant The Fell to Earth." p. 48-49
    -9/12/94 v. 27 # 36 (American Renaissance). "Critic's Choice." p. 121
    -10/3/94. v. 27 #39 (Cub Room, Café Centro). "Jolly, Stylish Bedlam." p.
    -10/10/94. v. 27 # 40 (Le Bernardin). "Starting Over." p. 44
    -10/17/94. v. 27 # 41 (Monkey Bar). "Bar Time for Bonzo." p. 99-100
    -10/24/94. v. 27 # 42 (Gramercy Tavern). "Hot, but Not Quite Haute."p. 76-77
    -11/14/94. v. 27 # 45 (Spartina). "The Lamb Shank Redemption." p. 90-91
    -11/28/94. v. 27 # 47 (Shun Lee Palace, Cafe Evergreen). "Beijing There." p. 90-91
    -12/12/94. v. 27 # 49 (Aja) "Lemongrass Roots." p. 88-89
  - January 2, 1995 - September 25, 1995 (Box 20)
    -1/2/95. Vol 28. #1 (Aja, American Renaissance, Aquavit, Arizona 206, Aureole, Barocco, Bar Pitti, Big Wong, Bo Ky, Bolo, owery Bar, Bureau, Café Centro and Beer Bar, Cafe Edison, Campagna, Carlyle Dining Room, Cascabel, China Fun (West), Christer's, Ciccio & Tony's, Circus, Coco Pazzo, C.T., Cucina & Company, Daniel, El Teddy's, Elaine's, Flowers, Four Seasons, Gabriel's Bar & Restaurant, Golden Unicorn, Gotham Bar & Grill, Gramercy Tavern, I Trulli, Jubilee, JUdson Grill, Le Bernardin, Le Cirque, Lespinasse, Manhattan Ocean Club, Match, MercBar, Michael's, Monkey Bar, Nick and Eddie, Nobu, Odeon, Park Avalon, Patria, Regency Restaurant, Remi, San Domenico, Sea Grill, Spartina, Taqueria de Mexico, Tai Hong Lau, 21, Virgil's Real Barbeque, West 63rd Street Steakhouse, Zarela). "Interview With a Restaurant Critic." p. 43-51
    -1/23/95. v. 28 #4 (Zarela, Rosa Mexicano, El Teddy's, Mi Cocina, El Rey del Sol, Rinconcito, Tacomadre, Taquería de Mexico, El Cantinero, Bright Food Shop, Pedro Páramo, Mi Tenampa, Samalita's Tortilla Factory, Plaza Garibaldi, Amanecer Ranchero, Tequilita's, Super Tacos, La China Poblana, Sombrero Cart, How Meals on Wheels, Tacos-El Parrandero, Lechon Lady's Cart, Stop One Supermarket, Mexico Lindo, Downtown Bakery, Azteca Deli, El Ranchito, Cowgirl Hall of Fame, Benny's Burritos, Fiesta Mexicana). The Whole Enchilada." p. 36-45
    -1/30/95. v. 28 #5 (American Renaissance). "Allusions of Grandeur." p. 79-81
    -2/20/95. v. 28 #8 (I Trulli & Filli Ponte). "Not Little Italy." p. 71-72
    -3/6/95. v. 28 # 10 (Zut! & Luma) "Rabbit Redux." p. 80-81
    -3/20/95. v. 28 # 12 (Aureole; Monkey Bar; Aja; Arizona 206; Le Chantilly;; Patria; Cascabel; Park Avenie Cafe) "Tall Orders." p. 52-56
    -4/10/95. v. 28 # 15 (Lex) "Bring Out the Hellman's." p. 76-77
    -4/17/95 NYM
    -4/24/95 v. 28 #17 (Alva) "Watt's Cooking?" p. 80-81
    -5/1/95 v. 28 # 18 (Bouley) "The Mania Event" p. 74 & 94
    -5/15/95 v. 28 # 20 (Lenox Room) "Uptown Airs" p. 70-71
    -5/29/95 v. 28 # 22 (Rain) "Nice Thai" p. 60-61
    -6/5/95 v. 28 # 23 (Bryant Park Grill and BP Cafe) "Forget Paris" p. 91-92
    -7/10/95 v. 28 # 27 (Ottoman Cuisine, Deniz, Turkish Kitchen) "Pita, Pita, Pita" p. 56-57
    -8/7/95 v. 28 # 31 (JUdson Grill) "Hype and Glory" p. 76-77
    -9/25/95 v. 28 # 38 (Bay Leaf) "Valley of the Dal" p. 118-119
  - October 2, 1995 - December 18, 1995 (Box 21)
    -10/2/95,NYM v. 28 # 39 (Lutece) "The Ghost and Mr. Muller" p. 86-87
    -10/9/95 ,NYM v. 28 # 40 (Kiosk, Zucca) "Eat, Media Darling, Eat" p. 96-97
    -10/16/95 NYM;v. 28 # 41 (Motown Cafe, Brooklyn Diner) "A Tale of Two Cities" p. 72-73
    -10/23/95 NYM,v. 28 #42 (Pomp, Duck & Circumstance) "Daffy Duck" p. 69-70
    -11/6/95 NYM, v. 28 #44 (13 Barrow St., Thompson St.) "The Global Village" p. 86-87
    -11/13/95 NYM, v. 28 #45 (La Côte Basque) "Côte Dependent" p. 92-94
    -11/20/95 NYM, v. 28 # 46 (Tapika) "Thoroughly Modern Chilies" p. 98-99
    -12/4/95NYM, v. 28 # 48 (Bouterin) "To Grand-mére's House" p. 151-152
    -12/11/95, NYM, v. 28 # 49 (Bar Anise, Lobster Club) "Price Clubs" p. 85-88
    -12/18/95NYM, v. 28 #50 (Layla) "Exotica" p. 60-61
  - January 8, 1996 - November 18, 1996 (Box 22)
    -1/8/96 NYM, vol 29 # 1 ( Alva, Arizona 206, Bar Anise, Bolo, Bouterin, Bowery Bar, Brooklyn Diner USA, Bryant Park Grill, Café Centro and Beer Bar, Campagna, Cascabel, Chelsea Bistro & Bar, Coco Pazzo, C.T., Daniel, Da Silvano, Dava, Da Vittorio, Eat and Drink, Fiftyseven Fiftyseven, The Four Seasons, Fresco by Scotto, Gotham Bar and Grill, Harry Cipriani, Hatsuhana, Home, Jekyll and Hyde, JUdson Grill, L'Absinthe, Layla, Le Bernardin, Le Cirque, The Lemon, Lenox Room, Lexpinasse, The Lobster Club, Luma, Lundy Bros. Restaurant, Mad.61, Mekong, Mesa Grill, Monkey Bar, MoTown Cafe, Nobu, Oceana, Official All-Star Cafe, Osteria del Circo, Patria, Picholine, Rain, Ratner's, Riodizio, San Domenico NY, Savann, Tapika, 13 Barrow St., Trattoria dell'Arte, Vong, Zucca, ) "Where to Eat Now" p. 28-35
    -1/29/96 v. 29 # 4 ( L'Absinthe, La Caravelle, La Côte Basque, Le Quercy, La Bonne Soupe, Les Pyrénées, René Pujol, Quartorze Bis, Café Centro, Restaurant Daniel, Le Cirque, Bouterin, Lutèce, La Luncheonette) "It's Déjà Vu All Over Again" p. 34-37
    -4/15/96 v. 29 # 15 Best of New York Issue (Le Bernardin) "Restaurant" p. 48 (Gotham Bar and Grill) "Eighties Throwback" p. 56
    -5/6/96 v. 29 # 18 (Osterica del Circo, Downtown) "Where the Boys Are" p. 90-92 (River) "Far East on the Upper West" Ask Gael p. 110
    -5/13/96 v. 29 #19 (Butterfield 81, Typhoon Brewery) "Cultural Exchange" p. 65-66 (Zeppole) "TriTrattoria" Ask Gael p. 85
    -5/20/96 v. 29 #20 (Sushi Bar, Sullivan's Restaurant and Broadcast Lounge) "Passion: Fish" p. 141-143 (Blue Water Grill) "Waterworld" Ask Gael p. 172
    -6/3/96 v. 29 # 22 (Marguery Grill, La Petite Rose) "The Comeback Kitchen" p. 98 & 144 (American Chef's Tribute to James Beard) "A Fair Deal" Ask Gael p. 119
    -6/10/96 v. 29 #23 (Solstice) "Changing the Lox" p. 57-58 (Mezze) "Publishing Magnet" Ask Gael p. 79
    -6/17/96 v. 29 #24 (Blue Water Grill, The Crab House) "Sea Change" p. 54-56 (Morton's of Chicago - Downtown) "Steak Exchange" p. 78
    -7/8/96 v. 29 # 26 (Ansonia) "Trading Up" p. 57-58 (Mesa Grill) "Noises Off" Ask Gael p. 79
    -7/22/96 v. 29 # 28 (Granville and E & O) "Two Darn Hot" p. 55-56 (The Boathouse Cafe) "Lakefront Property" Ask Gael p. 85
    -10/21/96 v. 29 # 41 (Mesa City) F: "The Spitfire Grill" p. 82-84: Ask Gael: (Charlie Trotter's Vegetables; Red, White & Greens: The Italian Way With Vegetables by Faith Willinger; The Pasta Bible by Christian Teubner, Silvio Rizzi & Tan Lee Leng) "Booking Dinner" In Print p. 107
    -10/28/96 v. 29 #42 (Mirezi) F: "Lo and Behold" p. 134-135 (Redeye Grill) "Do shrimp dance?" Ask Gael p. 161
    -11/4/96 v. 29 # 43 (The Screening Room), "Two Thumbs Up" 92&142 Malayboo) "Malayboo? Are you kidding?" Ask Gael p. 115
    -11/11/96 v.29 #44 (Celler in the Sky Canal House), "5 Wines, River Vu" p. 88-89 (Placido Domingo) "You don't write much about Spanish food" Ask Gael p. 112
    -11/18/96 v.29 #45 (Redeye Grill), Insatiable: "Kitsch of the Day" p.120-121Angelo & Maxie's) Ask Gael "Where are all the guys and dolls?"
  - December 2, 1996 - November 24, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    -12/2/96 v.29 #47 (Patroon/Angelo & Maxie's), Insatiable: "Let Them Eat Steak" p. 132/134/136 (Hot Tomato), "What's in a name?" Ask Gael p. 160
    -12/9/96 v.29 #48 (Quilty's, Candela), "Be It Ever So Humbert" p. 91-2 (Soul Cafe), "What's new and soulful?" Ask Gael p. 109
    -12/16/96 v.29 #49 (Ping's), Insatiable: "Ping Dynasty" p.68/70. (Casa La Femme), "Send us someplace romantic to nibble and neck" Ask Gael p.88
    -12/23-30/96 v.29 #50 (Wall St. Kitchen and Bar), "What's bullish on Wall Street?" Ask Gael p175.
    -1/6/97 V.29 #51 (Jean Georges, Jo Jo, Vong, The Independent, Balthazar, Restaurant 147, Two Rooms, Le Cirque 2000, Fresco, I Trulli, Bar Pitti, Wall Street Kitchen & Bar, Rao's, Il Mulino, Matthews, Cafe Centro, Osteria del Circo, Angelo and Maxie's, City Wine & Cigar Col, Fresco, Fred's, Virgil's Real BBQ, Maloney & Porcelli's, Bobby Van's, John's, Maloney & Porcelli, Circo, Spartina, Chat 'N Chew, Hot Tomato, Savann, Savann Est, 13 Barrow St., Circo, Luma, Indigo, Shun Lee Palace, Coco Pazzo Teatro, Firebird, Baraonda, Layla, Indochine, Pravda, Blue Water Grill, Restaurant 147, Sofia Fabulous Pizza, Marguery Grill, Mirezi, Quilty's, Ansonia, Sanzin, Mesa City, Redeye Grill, The Screening Room, Pizza Joint, Sassy's Sliders, Cellar in the Sky, Restaurant Two Two Two, Gotham Bar and Grill, Lespinasse, Daniel, Le Bernardin, Nobu, Mesa Grill, Bolo, Union Square Cafe, Aureole, Lenox Room, Patria, Picholine) F: "Dine Out On This", p.22-31
    -1/6/97 v.29 #51(Churrascaria Plataforma), "Why are all those guys running around with skewers?" Ask Gael p. 78.
    -4/14/97 Best of NY